It was an Axis Bank product or service.
Subscribe, like and subscribe to this video.
I am from here
and even after that it did not look that good.
Here we cannot say that. Subscribe
and if we talk about it, we should
subscribe. If you subscribe, you will definitely
get the same result. If we talk about a good person, then
Satyam will auto cut. He has
a pan above his feet. He presses f4
and Meghnad click. You may not be able to see anything here,
but 1969 things, we should
subscribe from here. He has
holdings on his surroundings. Smart Money in Trust,
both of these, so you will see this. First of all, for
basic banking, subscribe and subscribe to
the Channel. Please subscribe and
subscribe. Therefore, we will cut from here.
Subscribe to it. In this video,
if we talk about his husband, he is from
Africa, till 3858, it is excellent. Its one
around him is visible very little from there,
but focus on the things that are in front of you.
Its rising return on equity is very less. So,
like how is the child, then its
intake is breathable. When Bigg Boss was held after some time, it was
visible less there, then
you saw it.  It is giving, if we talk about
Kotak Mahindra Bank for an hour later,
mix both of them well,
if the risk of your life is less, then
talk about Kotak Mahindra Bank and HDFC Bank, do not forget to subscribe to our channel
and if you have not subscribed, quit
in one month, in three months,
in six months and do not forget to subscribe to Purna Sharma for six months
and subscribe, if you have
not
subscribed, then according to that, the
chutney of the bank did not increase, this
we have also seen in the swelling profile,
if we talk about this, see this,
subscribe to the channel,
like and if you talk about it, it came out that
if we talk about it, but the
utility there had gone, we had seen, if we
talk about Lakshmi, then again one should come down that
such a good chakli has been made around and some
improvements are seen increasing in it,
focus should be given here,
subscribe, definitely subscribe to the channel,
but secondly, let's read here,
[Music] is
more, 1.5 737 pass arrangement was seen coming
And in the entire global market, if you
show the pressure in feminist, all the levels are seen
coming, if the momentum is from here
and then a control city,
right now in the short term, momentum Fernandes,
but something can come in it at the moment,
hence the prime focus should come from here,
if the big Durg can reach around 150,
hence this hair can go to a limit at any time,
any short MP3 150 education can come very quickly,
but for a long time it is consolidating,
whenever you come out of the consolidation, it will
not take much time to reach that level,
lettuce, you know,
in this condition below 725, when Pooja Pradhan is in reference mind,
this is absolutely a good acquisition for
long term investment, come on friends, this
is not at all good in this video, we will meet
in the next video, till then you can subscribe to the channel,
thank you so much for this.